college english test band four part two
大学英语四级考试第二部分
Listening comprehension section a directions in this section
听力理解 A节 说明：在本节中
You will hear three news reports
你将听到三篇新闻报道
At the end of each news report
每篇新闻报道结束后
You'll hear two or three questions
你将听到两到三个问题
Both the news reports and the questions will be spoken only once
新闻报道和问题都只读一遍
After you hear a question
听完问题后
You must choose the best answer from the four choices marked a
你必须从标有A的四个选项中选出最佳答案
B , c and d
B、C和D
then mark the corresponding letter on answer
然后在答题卡上
Sheet one with a single line through the center
用横线划过相应字母
News report one
新闻报道一
the city of fayetteville is making a special effort to recognize its bus drivers
费耶特维尔市正在特别表彰其公交车司机
Ahead of the newly proclaimed transit driver appreciation day happening saturday
在新宣布的公交司机感谢日之前，该活动将于周六举行
As part of the event
作为活动的一部分
the city is celebrating its longest serving driver on the force
该市正在表彰车队中服务时间最长的司机
That driver is sherry christian
那位司机是谢丽·克里斯蒂安
Christian has been a driver for twenty five years
克里斯蒂安已经当了二十五年司机
The fayetville native believes driving a school bus
这位费耶特维尔本地人认为开校车
Allows her to give back to her community
让她能够回馈社区
She says that the best part of the job is watching the children who ride her bus grow up
她说这份工作最好的部分是看着乘坐她公交车的孩子们长大
Transit driver appreciation day has been celebrated across the country as far back as two thousand nine
公交司机感谢日早在2009年就在全国范围内庆祝
However , this week the city of fayetteville
然而，本周费耶特维尔市
Issued a proclamation for the day to take place march eighteenth
发布了一项公告，将这一天定在3月18日
Officials said they want bus drivers to know
官员们说他们想让公交司机知道
How important they are to faitville
他们对费耶特维尔有多重要
Serving almost one point six million riders a year
每年服务近160万乘客
Questions one and two are based on the news report you have just heard
问题一和问题二基于你刚才听到的新闻报道
Question one
问题一
What do we learn about sherry christian
关于谢丽·克里斯蒂安我们了解到什么
question two
问题二
what did city officials of faitville want bus drivers to be aware of
费耶特维尔市官员想让公交司机意识到什么
News report two
新闻报道二
The wilton school board has proposed a five point nine nine percent spending increase
威尔顿学校董事会提议增加5.99%的支出
If approved , it would be the largest jump in at least eight budget cycles
如果获得批准，这将是至少八个预算周期以来最大的增长
The five point nine nine percent request more than doubles
5.99%的请求超过了两倍
The highest previous year over year increase in the last eight years
过去八年中最高的一年同比增长
Which was two point nine nine percent
即2.99%
For the twenty twenty one to twenty twenty two school year
针对2021至2022学年
The biggest driver of the ninety one point eight million dollar proposed budget remains teachers salaries
9180万美元拟议预算的最大驱动因素仍然是教师工资
These account for sixty four percent of the total request at fifty nine million dollars
这占总请求的64%，即5900万美元
The fifty nine million dollars is up from the fifty six point seven million dollars
这5900万美元高于
Budgeted for the current school year
本学年的5670万美元预算
There are some factors that could affect the budget moving forward
有一些因素可能会影响未来的预算
One of those is total enrollment
其中之一是总入学人数
The district will have a total enrollment of three thousand seven hundred and forty two students
该学区将有3742名学生的总入学人数
Almost all of these students will be in kindergarten through high school
几乎所有这些学生将在幼儿园到高中
But sixty six will be in pre kindergarten and other programs
但66人将在学前班和其他项目中
This represents forty seven fewer students than the current year
这比本学年少了47名学生
Fewer students mean less federal and state funding
学生减少意味着联邦和州资助减少
Questions three and four are based on the news report you have just heard
问题三和问题四基于你刚才听到的新闻报道
Question three
问题三
What does the news report say the wilton school board has done
新闻报道说威尔顿学校董事会做了什么
question four
问题四
what will a decline in the total enrollment lead to
总入学人数下降会导致什么
News report three
新闻报道三
A rare thunder snow event has taken place in scotland
苏格兰发生了一场罕见的雷雪天气
And alarmed locals contacted police
惊慌的当地人联系了警方
Thinking they had heard bombs going off
以为他们听到了炸弹爆炸声
The phenomenon happens when thunder and lightning mix with a heavy snowstorm
这种现象发生在雷暴和大雪混合时
Sometimes causing loud collapse that can be confused with explosions
有时会产生巨大的声响，可能被误认为是爆炸
One person described it as a loud boom
有人将其描述为巨大的轰鸣声
Similar to a plane crash
类似于飞机坠毁
Another person was woken up in the middle of the night by what he thought was early construction work starting
另一个人在半夜被吵醒，以为是早期施工开始了
The noise was powerful enough to shake buildings and set off car alarms
噪音大到足以震动建筑物并触发汽车警报
The police were flooded with many calls from the public
警方接到了大量公众电话
And they sent out a message asking people to remain calm
他们发出信息要求人们保持冷静
The police assured everyone that it was just thunder and lightning
警方向所有人保证这只是雷暴
Rather than some military exercise
而不是某种军事演习
The weather was the coldest it had been for the season
这是本季最冷的天气
So people were warned to be careful when traveling outside
所以人们被警告在外出时要小心
In particular , dangerous conditions such as icy roads or wet ground
特别是冰冻道路或潮湿地面等危险情况
Could cause difficulty for drivers
可能会给司机带来困难
The rail service also announced potential disruptions to trains due to the deep snow
铁路服务也宣布由于大雪可能造成列车中断
Some roads were also closed because of the severe weather
一些道路也因恶劣天气而关闭
Questions five to seven are based on the news report you have just heard
问题五至问题七基于你刚才听到的新闻报道
Question five
问题五
What do we learn about thunder snows from the report
关于雷雪我们从报道中了解到什么
question six ： what did the police do when they received the local residents phone calls
问题六：当警方接到当地居民电话时做了什么
question seven . what were people advised to do when traveling outside
问题七。人们被建议在外出时做什么
Section b directions , in this section you will hear two long conversations
B节 说明：在本节中你将听到两段长对话
At the end of each conversation you will hear four questions
每段对话结束后你将听到四个问题
Both the conversation and the questions will be spoken only once
对话和问题都只读一遍
After you hear a question
听完问题后
You must choose the best answer from the four choices marked a
你必须从标有A的四个选项中选出最佳答案
B , c and d
B、C和D
Then mark the corresponding letter on answer sheet one with a single line through the center
然后在答题卡一上用横线划过相应字母
Conversation one
对话一
I'm going to the city centre to buy a new phone today
我今天要去市中心买一部新手机
Didn't you buy a new phone just two months ago
你不是两个月前才买了新手机吗
It was three months ago and i already know what you're going to say
是三个月前，我已经知道你要说什么了
You're thinking i shouldn't replace my phone this soon
你在想我不应该这么快换手机
No , actually i was wondering how you could possibly afford a new phone
不，实际上我在想你怎么可能买得起一部新手机
But now that you mention it
但现在你提到了
I do think getting another phone so soon is wasteful regardless of the cost
我确实认为这么快买另一部手机是浪费，不管成本如何
Maybe you're , right
也许你是对的
But the thing is everyone at the office has a nice expensive phone
但问题是办公室里每个人都有漂亮昂贵的手机
And i'm a little embarrassed by mine
我对我的有点尴尬
I just got a credit card
我刚办了一张信用卡
So i thought i might as well buy a new phone
所以我想我也可以买一部新手机
I don't think buying a phone on credit is a good idea
我认为用信用卡买手机不是个好主意
Look , you've only been working for five months now
听着，你才工作了五个月
People understand that you are a recent graduate
人们理解你是刚毕业的
And i doubt anyone cares about your phone other than yourself
我怀疑除了你自己，没人在乎你的手机
Maybe you're right
也许你是对的
But the credit card has a very good special offer
但这张信用卡有很好的优惠
Where i don't pay any interest for six months
六个月内我不付任何利息
I'll be able to pay for the phone
我可以在
Well before that period is over
那个期限结束前付清手机款
I still think it's a bad idea to use a credit card for something you don't need
我仍然认为用信用卡买你不需要的东西是个坏主意
one of my colleagues bought a lot of things on credit during her first year of work
我的一位同事在工作第一年用信用卡买了很多东西
And it became a bad habit
这成了一个坏习惯
And she accumulated a lot of debt
她积累了很多债务
Well , i can see how that might happen to someone
嗯，我能理解这可能会发生在某人身上
And i'm sure she regrets it
我相信她后悔了
But i know it won't happen to me
但我知道这不会发生在我身上
Questions eight to eleven are based on the conversation you have just heard
问题八至问题十一基于你刚才听到的对话
Question eight
问题八
What does the woman say she was actually wondering about
女子说她实际上在想什么
Question nine
问题九
why is the man a little embarrassed by the phone he's using now
为什么男子对他现在使用的手机有点尴尬
question ten
问题十
what does the man say about the credit card he just got
男子说他刚办的信用卡有什么优惠
question eleven
问题十一
what do we learn about one of the woman's colleagues
关于女子的一位同事我们了解到什么
Conversation two
对话二
Welcome to the morning show
欢迎来到晨间节目
Our guest today is a popular blog writer
今天的嘉宾是一位受欢迎的博客作家
And a major figure in the tiny home community
也是小房子社区的重要人物
Welcome bob jones
欢迎鲍勃·琼斯
Hi mary
嗨玛丽
Hi bob
嗨鲍勃
You're an advocate of the tiny home movement
你是小房子运动的倡导者
A lot of people don't know about this movement
很多人不了解这个运动
Can you tell our audience what it's about
你能告诉我们的观众它是关于什么的吗
Well , it's mainly about increasing home ownership and protecting the environment
嗯，它主要是关于增加住房拥有率和保护环境
Of course those are great goals
当然这些是很好的目标
but i've seen your blog
但我看过你的博客
And you write about houses that are as small as twenty square meters
你写的房子小到只有二十平方米
That's not a realistic size for families
这对家庭来说不是一个现实的大小
I do talk about very small homes
我确实谈论非常小的房子
But there's no set definition of a tiny home
但小房子没有固定的定义
And other people include homes that are much larger say sixty square meters
其他人包括更大的房子，比如六十平方米
And you'd be surprised
你会惊讶的
Many families of four are happy living in houses that are under thirty square metres
许多四口之家很乐意住在三十平方米以下的房子里
But i think most of us want spacious homes
但我认为我们大多数人都想要宽敞的房子
The average new house in this area is one hundred and fifty square meters
这个地区的新房平均是150平方米
And that's what people dream of owning
那是人们梦想拥有的
Yes
是的
But i think that dream needs to change
但我认为那个梦想需要改变
Considering the cost of housing
考虑到住房成本
Housing costs are high
住房成本很高
But do people really save that much by having a smaller home
但人们真的通过拥有更小的房子节省那么多吗
Absolutely
当然
Many people who can only afford to rent a larger home
许多只能租得起大房子的人
Are able to buy a tiny home
能够买得起小房子
In this city , the average home costs two hundred thousand dollars
在这个城市，平均房价是20万美元
And a tiny home costs just fifty thousand dollars
而小房子只需5万美元
Those are huge savings
这是巨大的节省
So tiny homes might not be for everyone
所以小房子可能不适合每个人
But there a good option for many
但对许多人来说是个好选择
You mentioned the environment earlier
你之前提到了环境
How does this benefit the planet
这对地球有什么好处
Well , if people have smaller homes
嗯，如果人们有更小的房子
They use less land and fewer resources to build them
他们使用更少的土地和更少的资源来建造
Questions twelve to fifteen are based on the conversation you have just heard
问题十二至问题十五基于你刚才听到的对话
Question twelve
问题十二
What does the tiny home movement mainly advocate
小房子运动主要倡导什么
Question thirteen what does the woman say about houses as small as twenty square meters
问题十三 女子关于小到二十平方米的房子说了什么
Question fourteen
问题十四
what does the man think about the dream of owning a one hundred fifty square meter house
男子对拥有150平方米房子的梦想怎么看
question fifteen
问题十五
what does the man say about tiny homes
男子关于小房子说了什么
Section c directions , in this section
C节 说明：在本节中
You will hear three passages
你将听到三篇文章
At the end of each passage
每篇文章结束后
You will hear three or four questions
你将听到三到四个问题
Both the passage and the questions will be spoken only once
文章和问题都只读一遍
After you hear a question
听完问题后
You must choose the best answer from the four choices marked a
你必须从标有A的四个选项中选出最佳答案
B , c and d
B、C和D
Then mark the corresponding letter on answer
然后在答题卡上
Sheet one with a single line through the center passage one
用横线划过相应字母 文章一
Kids need time every day to run
孩子们每天需要时间奔跑
Jump , stretch and play
跳跃、伸展和玩耍
These experiences have been shown to build children's confidence and pleasure in physical activities
这些体验已被证明可以建立孩子对体育活动的信心和乐趣
Develop their motor skills , and even improve emotional wellbeing
发展他们的运动技能，甚至改善情绪健康
To begin with , children seem to have a natural desire to overcome challenges and take risks
首先，孩子们似乎有克服挑战和冒险的自然欲望
Taking healthy risks through physical movement
通过体育活动进行健康冒险
Builds children's confidence and ability to solve problems and persist through frustration
建立孩子的信心和解决问题的能力，以及克服挫折的毅力
Secondly , movement activities build children's big body skills
其次，运动活动建立孩子的大肌肉技能
Such as coordination and balance
如协调和平衡
As well as the fine motor skills they need for tasks like writing
以及他们完成任务所需的精细运动技能，如写字
Tying their shoes or throwing and catching a ball
系鞋带或投接球
Thirdly , according to the american psychological association
第三，根据美国心理学会
Regular physical activity and especially outdoor activity
定期体育活动，尤其是户外活动
Reduces children's stress and depression
可以减少孩子的压力和抑郁
And improve their ability to focus and learn
提高他们专注和学习的能力
Regular exercise can significantly improve self regulation
定期运动可以显著改善自我调节
And decrease disciplinary consequences for negative behaviour
减少负面行为的纪律后果
Physical activity provides a positive outlet for frustration
体育活动为挫折提供了积极的出口
Anxiety or anger
焦虑或愤怒
And can become a healthy coping skill throughout life
可以成为一生的健康应对技能
Finally , we know that physical activity is important for our physical and mental health
最后，我们知道体育活动对我们的身心健康很重要
And cultivating the habit of physical activity starts early
培养体育活动的习惯从小开始
Children are more likely to develop a lifelong
孩子更有可能从频繁的积极早期体验中
Love of physical activity from frequent positive early experiences
培养终身的体育活动爱好
Not every child enjoys competitive sports or playing with balls and that's okay
不是每个孩子都喜欢竞技运动或玩球，这没关系
There are plenty of other options
有很多其他选择
Such as imaginative play
如想象游戏
Non competitive games and gardening or nature experiences
非竞技游戏和园艺或自然体验
Questions sixteen to eighteen are based on the passage you have just heard
问题十六至问题十八基于你刚才听到的文章
Question sixteen
问题十六
What do children seem to have a natural desire to do
孩子们似乎有什么自然的欲望
Question seventeen according to the american psychological association
问题十七 根据美国心理学会
What does regular physical activity do to children
定期体育活动对孩子有什么作用
Question eighteen what does the passage say about cultivating the habit of physical activity
问题十八 文章关于培养体育活动习惯说了什么
Passage two
文章二
A new study finds that job seekers are even willing to explore jobs with lower salaries
一项新研究发现，当公司更加多元化时
When companies are more diverse
求职者甚至愿意探索薪资较低的工作
It finds that sharing information about diversity
它发现分享多元化信息
Makes job postings more attractive to job seekers
使职位发布对求职者更有吸引力
Even when pay is lower
即使薪资较低
To conduct this study
为了进行这项研究
The team partnered with an online job listings platform
团队与一个在线职位发布平台合作
Which emails postings relevant to individuals and their job search criteria
该平台根据个人求职标准发送相关职位信息
For the course of the eleven week study
在为期十一周的研究中
The platform emailed job listines to some one hundred and eighty thousand users
该平台向约十八万用户发送职位信息
Placed in one of two conditions
分为两种情况
In the baseline condition
在基准情况中
Participants saw emails in the normal format with no information on diversity
参与者看到正常格式的电子邮件，没有多元化信息
In the diversity condition
在多元化情况中
Participants saw a diversity score for each listing
参与者看到每个职位的多元化评分
Information about the race
关于种族的信息
Gender , education , and language skills of a company's workforce
公司员工的性别、教育和语言技能
Compared to others in the same sector , and location
与同一行业和地区的其他公司相比
Information was then gathered on whether the email was opened
然后收集关于电子邮件是否被打开的信息
And which job listings were clicked on by each user
以及每个用户点击了哪些职位发布
Participants in the diversity condition
多元化情况中的参与者
tended to click on job
倾向于点击
Listings from companies with slightly higher diversity
多元化评分略高的公司的职位
Scores than those in the baseline condition
比基准情况中的参与者
That is , participants seem to be paying attention to information about diversity
也就是说，参与者似乎在关注多元化信息
And using this when deciding whether to click on the listing
并在决定是否点击职位时使用这些信息
and the team also found that participants were willing to look at listines with lower salaries
团队还发现，参与者愿意查看薪资较低的职位
If they came from companies with a higher diversity score
如果这些职位来自多元化评分较高的公司
Questions nineteen to twenty one are based on the passage you have just heard
问题十九至问题二十一基于你刚才听到的文章
Question nineteen
问题十九
When are job seekers willing to explore jobs with lower salaries
根据一项新研究，求职者什么时候愿意探索薪资较低的工作
According to a new study
根据一项新研究
Question twenty what did participants see in the baseline condition of the study
问题二十 在研究的基准情况中，参与者看到了什么
question twenty one what does the passage say participants seem to be paying attention to
问题二十一 文章说参与者似乎在关注什么
Passage three
文章三
A new study from oregon state university
俄勒冈州立大学的一项新研究
Found that dogs tend to match their behaviour with the children in their family
发现狗倾向于与家庭中的孩子匹配行为
The findings are important
这些发现很重要
Because there is a growing body of evidence that dogs can help children in many ways
因为有越来越多的证据表明狗可以在许多方面帮助孩子
These include helping with social development
这些包括帮助社交发展
Increasing physical activity
增加体育活动
Managing anxiety , or serving as a source of attachment in the
管理焦虑，或在家庭结构变化时作为依恋来源
Face of changing family structures
面对变化的家庭结构
Yet very little research has focused on
然而，很少有研究关注
How dogs perceive and socially engage with children
狗如何感知和与孩子社交互动
The great news is that this study suggests
好消息是，这项研究表明
Dogs are paying a lot of attention to the kids that they live with
狗非常关注与它们一起生活的孩子
Said monique adele , the lead author of the study
该研究的主要作者莫妮克·阿黛尔说
One interesting thing we have observed is that dogs are matching children's behavior
我们观察到的一件有趣的事情是，狗正在匹配孩子的行为
But less frequently than what we have seen between dogs and adults
但频率低于我们在狗和成人之间看到的
This suggests that wild dogs may view children as social companions
这表明野生狗可能将孩子视为社交伙伴
There are also some differences that we need to understand better
还有一些我们需要更好理解的差异
While research has found dogs can have a lot of positive impacts on a child's life
虽然研究发现狗可以对孩子的生活产生很多积极影响
There are also risks associated with a dog child relationship
狗与孩子的关系也存在风险
For example
例如
Other studies have found dogs are more likely to bite children versus adults
其他研究发现狗比成人更容易咬孩子
We still have a lot to learn about the dog child relationship
我们仍然有很多关于狗与孩子关系的东西要学习
Adele said
阿黛尔说
But research does show that kids are very capable of training docks
但研究确实表明，孩子非常有能力训练狗
Questions twenty two to twenty five are based on the passage you have just heard
问题二十二至问题二十五基于你刚才听到的文章
Question twenty two
问题二十二
What does the passage say about the findings of a new study from oregon state university
文章关于俄勒冈州立大学新研究的发现说了什么
Question twenty three what does a growing body of evidence show according to the passage
问题二十三 根据文章，越来越多的证据显示什么
question twenty four what did moniku del say their study suggests
问题二十四 莫妮克·德尔说他们的研究暗示了什么
question twenty five
问题二十五
what does research show kids are very capable of doing
研究显示孩子非常有能力做什么
that's the end of listening comprehension
听力理解部分结束